<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><LanguageData><FB_BecomeFleshHeart.description>Sacrifice your physical form to transform into the Flesh Heart — a pulsating biomass core that begins the expansion.</FB_BecomeFleshHeart.description><FB_BecomeFleshHeart.label>Become the Flesh Heart</FB_BecomeFleshHeart.label><FB_BodyPartTransfer.description>Transfer a missing body part from a dead target to restore your own missing part.</FB_BodyPartTransfer.description><FB_BodyPartTransfer.label>body part transfer</FB_BodyPartTransfer.label><FB_CallEscort.description>Calls nearby creatures to the caster. They approach and escort the caster for a while.</FB_CallEscort.description><FB_CallEscort.label>call escort</FB_CallEscort.label><FB_CocoonFlesh.description>Encases the selected pawn in a living biomass cocoon, drawing them closer to the nature of the flesh creatures. While inside, the pawn undergoes transformation, evolving with a new trait aligned to the Flesh.</FB_CocoonFlesh.description><FB_CocoonFlesh.label>Cocoon of Flesh</FB_CocoonFlesh.label><FB_ConvertCorpseToParasiteEgg.description>Transform the target body into the egg of a personal parasite. Works exclusively when studying the relevant technology; without it, it explodes the body.</FB_ConvertCorpseToParasiteEgg.description><FB_ConvertCorpseToParasiteEgg.label>convert to parasite egg</FB_ConvertCorpseToParasiteEgg.label><FB_GrowArmor.description>Grow a temporary chitinous armor from your own flesh. This organic plating provides enhanced protection against attacks but deteriorates over time, eventually crumbling away. It may impair mobility and appearance while active.</FB_GrowArmor.description><FB_GrowArmor.label>grow armor</FB_GrowArmor.label><FB_ParasiteCall.description>Calls all matured parasites implanted in targets to burst out immediately during danger, spawning combat-ready entities to aid the carrier.</FB_ParasiteCall.description><FB_ParasiteCall.label>parasite call</FB_ParasiteCall.label><FB_ParasiteImplant.description>Implants a maturing parasite into the target's torso by sacrificing one of the carrier's fingers. The parasite develops over time and can be called to burst out in combat when ready.</FB_ParasiteImplant.description><FB_ParasiteImplant.label>implant parasite</FB_ParasiteImplant.label><FB_Scavenger.description>Transforms a fresh corpse into one or more DenseWeaver creatures, triggering a small meat explosion effect.</FB_Scavenger.description><FB_Scavenger.label>scavenger</FB_Scavenger.label><FB_FleshDivision.description>Split the caster into a second body. Both resulting pawns keep only half of the original age and half of every skill's earned experience. Worn apparel is shed to the ground, and both bodies become temporarily flesh-unstable.</FB_FleshDivision.description><FB_FleshDivision.label>flesh division</FB_FleshDivision.label><FB_FleshDivision.confirmationDialogText>Start flesh division? This will split the pawn into two unstable bodies, halve age and skill experience, and drop worn apparel.</FB_FleshDivision.confirmationDialogText>
  <FB_Bloodlash.label>bloodlash</FB_Bloodlash.label>
  <FB_Bloodlash.description>Unleashes a blood tendril from the caster's throat to latch onto a nearby living target and begin draining blood. The stolen blood feeds the caster and helps restore blood loss or hemogen reserves.</FB_Bloodlash.description>

  <FB_SpineLaunch_TentacleTurret.label>spine launch</FB_SpineLaunch_TentacleTurret.label>
  <FB_SpineLaunch_TentacleTurret.description>Launches a keratin spine at a distant target.</FB_SpineLaunch_TentacleTurret.description>
</LanguageData>